<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<portfolio>
	<item>
		<types>
			<type>photo</type>
		</types>
		<title><![CDATA[Rooms in the Rainforest Retreat]]></title>
		<company><![CDATA[Rainforest Retreat]]></company>
		<date>March 2020</date>
		<photo>rainforest2.jpg</photo>
		<description><![CDATA[Deep In the heart of west coast glacier country, Rainforest Retreat offers a range of accommodation set amongst lush native bush in the Franz Josef township. From luxury tree huts to backpackers rooms.<br> It was a short project where I took photos of a couple of rooms that ended up on their website.]]></description>
		<tags>
			<tag>#interior</tag>
		</tags>
		<link>#</link>
	</item>

	<item>
		<types>
			<type>photo</type>
		</types>
		<title><![CDATA[New Year in Franz Josef Glacier]]></title>
		<company><![CDATA[Monsoon Bar & Restaurant]]></company>
		<date>December 2019</date>
		<photo>monsoon.jpg</photo>
		<description><![CDATA[With roaring fires & regular DJ’s, Monsoon bar carries a large range of New Zealand finest beers and wines, while the Monsoon restaurant satisfies hunger whatever the budget with all you can eat pizza nights, bar meals and an à la carte menu.<br>Great Gatsby themed night and a live DJ was a perfect way to ring in 2020. My job as the official photographer was to capture the spirit of the roaring 20s and make memories for the guests while maintaining the photo booth. Click here if you want to check out the highlihts.]]></description>
		<tags>
			<tag>#event</tag>
		</tags>
		<link>#</link>
	</item>

	<item>
		<types>
			<type>video</type>
			<type>photo</type>
		</types>
		<title><![CDATA[Videographer at CCIS]]></title>
		<company><![CDATA[Chamber of Commerce and Industry of Slovenia]]></company>
		<date>2019</date>
		<photo>gzs.jpg</photo>
		<description><![CDATA[The Chamber of Commerce and Industry of Slovenia is a non-governmental organisation representing the interests of the Slovenian economy. It provides essential services for enterprises operating in Slovenia. For the organisations I produced over 50 videos (presentations and reportages) for various events organised by the chamber.<br><i style="font-size: 15px;">“For the Chamber of Commerce and Industry of Slovenia’s online television (tv.GZS), Damjan Pjević has recorded, edited, photographed and managed to broadcast various events throughout the year. He worked diligently, was a friendly and communicative associate. Showed accuracy, precision and reliability in his work. Finished products were of high quality and always met, and often exceeded our expectations.” – Branka Murn, Managing editor at the tv.GZS</i>]]></description>
		<tags>
			<tag>#event</tag>
			<tag>#portraits </tag>
			<tag>#broadcasting</tag>
		</tags>	
		<link>#</link>
	</item>	

	<item>
		<types>
			<type>video</type>
		</types>
		<title><![CDATA[Mladi Pomurci: Ta noč bo najina]]></title>
		<company><![CDATA[Ansambel Mladi Pomurci]]></company>
		<date>June 2019</date>
		<photo>mpNoc2.jpg</photo>
		<description><![CDATA[Produced the second official music video for the young volkmusik band of five. The polka “This night will be ours” tells a love story between a young couple caught between the day and the night; the sea and the stars. As the videographer, my job was to record, edit and help with the production of the music video. Click here to check it out.]]></description>
		<tags>
			<tag>#musicVideo</tag>
		</tags>
		<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=X5LjJ0JqVxY</link>
	</item>	

	<item>
		<types>
			<type>video</type>
		</types>
		<title><![CDATA[Mladi Pomurci: Svet postal bi lep]]></title>
		<company><![CDATA[Ansambel Mladi Pomurci]]></company>
		<date>May 2019</date>
		<photo>mpSvet.jpg</photo>
		<description><![CDATA[The first offical music video I filmed for the young band.]]></description>
		<tags>
			<tag>#musicVideo</tag>
		</tags>
		<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=h4evc9qe_zs</link>
	</item>	

	<item>
		<types>
			<type>photo</type>
		</types>
		<title><![CDATA[Oktoberfest]]></title>
		<company><![CDATA[Festanation]]></company>
		<date>September 2018</date>
		<photo>oktoberfest.jpg</photo>
		<description><![CDATA[The three weeks I spent in München, Germany were absolutely incredible. Festanation is a pop-up hostel where travelers can meet like-minded fun havers such as themselves. This time they pop-upped in the world’s most legendary and biggest beer festival. My job as their official photographer was to capture the heart of the festival and fun memories for our guests. Both of which were shared daily on social media. To check out the highlights, click here. Ein prosit!
		<br><i style="font-size: 15px;">“We have a phrase in English to describe someone like Damjan, and that is that he truly is a 'gentleman and a scholar'. Kind-hearted, diligent and with a great work ethic, we brought Damjan in as a photographer for our event and we weren't disappointed as he created some real visual memories for both the crew and the guests with his work. Well loved and respected by his peers, Damjan would be a real asset to anyone looking for similar experiences. Not afraid to get stuck in, join in with the activities as part of either a small or a large group, we loved having Damjan as part of our crew for this event and would love to have him back for anything in future if he was ever keen.” – Mark Larwood, GM for Festanation</i>]]></description>
		<tags>
			<tag>#event</tag>
		</tags>
		<link>#</link>
	</item>	
	<item>
		<types>
			<type>photo</type>
		</types>
		<title><![CDATA[Funky Disco Soul Pop Party]]></title>
		<company><![CDATA[Groovocado]]></company>
		<date>May 2018</date>
		<photo>groovo1.jpg</photo>
		<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
		<tags>
			<tag>#concert</tag>
		</tags>
		<link>#</link>
	</item>	
	<item>
		<types>
			<type>photo</type>
			<type>video</type>
		</types>
		<title><![CDATA[Iceland 2018]]></title>
		<company><![CDATA[Canon Slovenia]]></company>
		<date>April 2018</date>
		<photo>iceland.jpg</photo>
		<description><![CDATA[With two friends, I spend a week and a half in one of the most beautiful places in the world. From ice-cold glaciers and waterfalls that pour over every cliff to rugged landscapes and natural hot springs, Iceland is surely a place where nature reigns supreme. For the trip, Canon Slovenia provided us with Canon's brand-new camera and gear. While travelling, they frequently shared our photos and vlogs on their social media platforms. Click here to check out a couple of highlights]]></description>
		<tags>
			<tag>#travel</tag>
		</tags>
		<link>#</link>
	</item>	
</portfolio>

<!--
	<item>
		<types>
			<type></type>
		</types>
		<title><![CDATA[]]></title>
		<company><![CDATA[]]></company>
		<date></date>
		<photo></photo>
		<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
		<tags>
			<tag></tag>
		</tags>
		<link>#</link>
	</item>	
	-->